{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Systems Integration and Architecture",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": "Fifth Module",
    "LastModified": "17 May 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "JC"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Any external links/handouts should be referenced here"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the process of aligning demand with manufacturing capacity in creating production and procurement \r\nschedules for the finished products and component materials?",
      "answer": "Production Planning",
      "choices": [
        "Production Planning",
        "Materials Management",
        "Sales and Distribution",
        "Financial Accounting"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is what you call the independent environment in the system.",
      "answer": "Client",
      "choices": [
        "Client",
        "Plant",
        "Storage Location",
        "Company Code"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(?????) is the smallest organizational unit where a legal set of books can be maintained.",
      "answer": "Company Code",
      "choices": [
        "Company Code",
        "Plant",
        "Storage Location",
        "Client"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(?????) is the operating area or branch within the company, such as manufacturing, distribution, purchasing, or maintenance facility.",
      "answer": "Plant",
      "choices": [
        "Plant",
        "Client",
        "Storage Location",
        "Company Code"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(?????) allows differentiation between the various stocks of material in a plant.",
      "answer": "Storage Location",
      "choices": [
        "Storage Location",
        "Plant",
        "Work Center Locations",
        "Company Code"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(?????) define where and when the operation is performed. These can be machines, people, production lines, or groups of tradespeople.",
      "answer": "Work Center Locations",
      "choices": [
        "Work Center Locations",
        "Client",
        "Storage Location",
        "Company Code"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This master data contains all the information a company needs to manage a material.",
      "answer": "Material Master",
      "choices": [
        "Material Master",
        "Bill of Materials",
        "Routing",
        "Work Center"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This master data lists the component that make up a product or assembly.",
      "answer": "Bill of Materials",
      "choices": [
        "Material Master",
        "Bill of Materials",
        "Routing",
        "Work Center"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the series of sequential steps or operations that must be carried out to produce a given product.",
      "answer": "Routing",
      "choices": [
        "Material Master",
        "Bill of Materials",
        "Routing",
        "Work Center"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the location within a plant where Value-added work is performed.",
      "answer": "Work Center",
      "choices": [
        "Material Master",
        "Bill of Materials",
        "Routing",
        "Work Center"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is aggregate planning that group materials or other product groups.",
      "answer": "Product Group",
      "choices": [
        "Product Group",
        "Bill of Materials",
        "Material Master",
        "Work Center"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the three different kinds of Bill of Materials?",
      "answer": "Single-level, Multi-level, Variant",
      "choices": [
        "Single-level, Multi-level, Variant",
        "Single-level, Double-level, Multi-level",
        "Single-level, Multi-level, Variance",
        "One-level, Multi-level, Variant"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(?????) is the foundation of a reliable Sales and Operations Planning (SOP). Accurate (?????) are essential in the \r\nmanufacturing sector, which could help oversee the stock since overstocked and understocked warehouses \r\nboth result in a profit loss",
      "answer": "Forecasting",
      "choices": [
        "Forecasting",
        "Guessing",
        "Planning",
        "Imagining"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following aren't part of the Forecasting Model?",
      "answer": "Fads",
      "choices": [
        "Fads",
        "Trend",
        "Seasonal",
        "Constant"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(?????) serves as the link between the Strategic Planning and Detailed Planning layers in Production Planning and Execution",
      "answer": "Demand Management",
      "choices": [
        "Demand Management",
        "Demand Program",
        "Demand Planning",
        "Demand"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(?????) allows a company to distinguish planning methods between materials that strongly influence profit or use \r\ncritical resources and those that do not.",
      "answer": "Master Production Scheduling",
      "choices": [
        "Master Production Scheduling",
        "Master Requirement Planning",
        "Production Order",
        "Master Production Execution"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "In (?????), the system calculates the net requirements while considering available warehouse stock and scheduled receipts from purchasing and production. During (?????), all levels of the bill of material are planned.",
      "answer": "Master Requirement Planning",
      "choices": [
        "Master Production Scheduling",
        "Master Requirement Planning",
        "Production Order",
        "Master Production Execution"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1"
    }
  ]
}
